{"test_questions": [[{"question": "Data scrubbing is which of the following?", "opta": "A process to reject data from the data warehouse and to create the necessary indexes", "optb": "A process to load the data in the data warehouse and to create the necessary indexes", "optc": "A process to upgrade the quality of data after it is moved into a data warehouse", "optd": "A process to upgrade the quality of data before it is moved into a data warehouse", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The @active data warehouse architecture includes which of the following?", "opta": "At least one data mart", "optb": "Data that can extracted from numerous internal and external sources", "optc": "Near real-time updates", "optd": "All of the above.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A goal of data mining includes which of the following?", "opta": "To explain some observed event or condition", "optb": "To confirm that data exists", "optc": "To analyze data for expected relationships", "optd": "To create a new data warehouse", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "An operational system is which of the following?", "opta": "A system that is used to run the business in real time and is based on historical data.", "optb": "A system that is used to run the business in real time and is based on current data.", "optc": "A system that is used to support decision making and is based on current data.", "optd": "A system that is used to support decision making and is based on historical data.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A data warehouse is which of the following?", "opta": "Can be updated by end users.", "optb": "Contains numerous naming conventions and formats.", "optc": "Organized around important subject areas.", "optd": "Contains only current data.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A snowflake schema is which of the following types of tables?", "opta": "Fact", "optb": "Dimension", "optc": "Helper", "optd": "All of the above", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The generic two-level data warehouse architecture includes which of the following?", "opta": "At least one data mart", "optb": "Data that can extracted from numerous internal and external sources", "optc": "Near real-time updates", "optd": "All of the above.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Fact tables are which of the following?", "opta": "Completely denoralized", "optb": "Partially denoralized", "optc": "Completely normalized", "optd": "Partially normalized", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Data transformation includes which of the following?", "opta": "A process to change data from a detailed level to a summary level", "optb": "A process to change data from a summary level to a detailed level", "optc": "Joining data from one source into various sources of data", "optd": "Separating data from one source into various sources of data", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Reconciled data is which of the following?", "opta": "Data stored in the various operational systems throughout the organization.", "optb": "Current data intended to be the single source for all decision support systems.", "optc": "Data stored in one operational system in the organization.", "optd": "Data that has been selected and formatted for end-user support applications.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The load and index is which of the following?", "opta": "A process to reject data from the data warehouse and to create the necessary indexes", "optb": "A process to load the data in the data warehouse and to create the necessary indexes", "optc": "A process to upgrade the quality of data after it is moved into a data warehouse", "optd": "A process to upgrade the quality of data before it is moved into a data warehouse", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The extract process is which of the following?", "opta": "Capturing all of the data contained in various operational systems", "optb": "Capturing a subset of the data contained in various operational systems", "optc": "Capturing all of the data contained in various decision support systems", "optd": "Capturing a subset of the data contained in various decision support systems", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A star schema has what type of relationship between a dimension and fact table?", "opta": "Many-to-many", "optb": "One-to-one", "optc": "One-to-many", "optd": "All of the above.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Transient data is which of the following?", "opta": "Data in which changes to existing records cause the previous version of the records to be eliminated", "optb": "Data in which changes to existing records do not cause the previous version of the records to be eliminated", "optc": "Data that are never altered or deleted once they have been added", "optd": "Data that are never deleted once they have been added", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A multifield transformation does which of the following?", "opta": "Converts data from one field into multiple fields", "optb": "Converts data from multiple fields into one field", "optc": "Converts data from multiple fields into multiple fields", "optd": "All of the above", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}